SERGE CHURKIN

WEB DEVELOPER

WWW.SERGE-WEB.COM

289-501-7013
SERGECHURKIN@GMAIL.COM
TORONTO, ON
GITHUB

LINKEDIN

SKILLS

- HTML5, CSS3
- SASS
- Responsive design
- JavaScript
- React.js
- Restful APIs
- GitHub
- jQuery
- Node.js, Express
- Firebase, MySQL
- MS Excel VBA, Google sheets and Google Maps API
- WordPress
- Linux
- Photo and Video Editing
- Leadership
- Complex problem solving
- Project Management
- Customer Service
- Analytics
- Email Distribution

PROFILE

Web Developer who is building accessible and responsive web applications primarily using front-end technologies. Backed by a background in operations management, I leverage my extensive experience in leading complex tasks and problem-solving to develop performant web interfaces.

PROJECTS

- Tour Agency Inventory | React, Firebase database. This app helps to manipulate tour data by adding, removing and editing an inventory in the table, updated information renders in real-time on the user's page. |
 Code | Live
- Recipe Generator | JavaScript, API, jQuery. This app accesses recipe API data to provide recipe suggestions based on the user's input of ingredients selection. |
 Code | Live
- Country Quiz | JavaScript, SCSS. This app is a multiplechoice fun quiz and analyzes the data inputted by the user, based on answers about the countries specifics, interests and character | Code | Live

EDUCATION

JUNO COLLEGE OF TECHNOLOGY

TORONTO, ON | 2020

- Web Development Immersive Certificate (Bootcamp) | Jun 2020 - Sept 202
- Introduction to Web Development | May 2020
- Javascript | Mar 2020 April 2020

NIAGARA COLLEGE CANADA

NIAGARA FALLS, ON | 2016-2018

- International Business Management
- Tourism and Hospitality Management

WORK EXPERIENCE

FREELANCE WEB DEVELOPER | FEB 2021 - PRESENT

FALLSVIEW GROUP OF HOTELS | NIAGARA FALLS, ON

AUDIT SUPERVISOR | MAY 2018 - JAN 2020

- Improved processing of daily financial and balancing reports from 5 to 1.5 hrs
- Maximized revenue and ensured 101% hotel occupancy with 200 rooms by overselling, monitoring reservations, and updating rates
- Supervised and trained 2 auditors, shared best practices and trained booking system and reporting

AUDITOR | AUG 2016 - MAY 2018

- Reconciled, audited, and balanced accounts, prepared revenue reports in a hotel with 600 rooms
- Checked in guests, answered the calls and instant messages, ensured a high standard of service